module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who is the spokesperson of Icy Hot?', 
    a: 'Ben Stein',
    b: 'Common',
    c: 'Shaquille O\'Neal',
    d: 'Stephen Colbert',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is not an Atlassian product?', 
    a: 'Trello',
    b: 'Basecamp',
    c: 'Confluence',
    d: 'Jira',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Vince Offer was the pitchman for what product?', 
    a: 'ShamWow',
    b: 'Oxiclean',
    c: 'Snuggie',
    d: 'Magic Bullet',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following HTML tags would you use to create a list with each item numbered?', 
    a: '<ol>',
    b: '<ul>',
    c: '<nl>',
    d: '<dl>',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What company makes Oreos?', 
    a: 'General Mills',
    b: 'Nabisco',
    c: 'Nestle',
    d: 'Pillsbury',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who composed "The Nutcracker"?', 
    a: 'Handel',
    b: 'Beethoven',
    c: 'Mozart',
    d: 'Tchaikovsky',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The pH of pure water is approximately:', 
    a: '2',
    b: '4',
    c: '7',
    d: '10',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which company was Elon Musk never involed in?', 
    a: 'Solar City',
    b: 'The Boring Company',
    c: 'PayPal',
    d: 'Tumblr',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What sushi does not contain any seafood?', 
    a: 'Unagi',
    b: 'Dragon Roll',
    c: 'California Roll',
    d: 'Tiger Roll',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What liquid is found in most cigarette lighters?', 
    a: 'Butane',
    b: 'Gasoline',
    c: 'Kerosene',
    d: 'Propane',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];